The morning chimes have sounded. We are Wisdom Tianwu City Junior High School.
From now on, we will hold the 2023 cold Chinese noodles draft.
Everyone bow.
Here are the ingredients to put on top of the chilled Chinese noodles.
I would like to take a look at them, if that's alright with you all.
Yes, I understand.
This way is what kind of menchis are sitting here.
I see...
From here?
From here, we're going to sit on the munchies.
This is...
Chilled Chinese noodles.
Noodle W
Udon
Soba
and Kimchi
Kani Kama
Do you put crabcakes?
It was also in our chilled Chinese noodles.
Oh, really?
Tomato
Red ginger
Fish sausage
Is this yakitori?
Canned yakitori
Ham
Chashu pork.
Cucumber, lettuce, green onion
Eggs
Corn Corn
Yellow bell peppers
And this irregular member
Cucumber and pineapple
Is there anyone else in the group? At home?
I don't see any.
No, I don't think so.
So it's fresh for one of us?
I don't know.
But why don't you try it?
Oh, no.
Psychological warfare has begun.
I thought it was delicious.
I knew it.
To be adventurous like this.
It's so...
JK's got a thing for that.
Is that what you mean?
Did you say that?
Oh, no.
The most traditional way to make chilled Chinese noodles is to make chilled Chinese noodles.
Chinese noodles, cucumber, egg, red ginger, chashu pork and chilled chuka sauce.
We have 4 kinds of sauce!
Chilled Chinese sauce, Sesame sauce, Mentsuyu, and Curry!
Curry
Curry?
It tastes like udon noodles!
Chilled Chinese noodles.
Can I choose one of my favorites?Can I pick one of my favorites?
Yeah. - Wow.
Wow, I wonder what's so important.
I'm starting to think it's not the noodles.
The noodles are...
Worst case scenario, they're all good.
Unless someone takes all the noodles.
They're all good, aren't they?
Yes.
Oh, you mean you can interrupt
But instead of members
I'm doing tea rice udon or something like that.
You're sacrificing yourself to get in the way of others.
Let's do it.
Let's start the chilled Chinese noodles draft.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Now, everyone, please write down your first choice of ingredients on the white board.
Yes, sir.
I thought I'd buy the one that goes with everything.
Yes, yes, that's right. That's right, that's right.
What about JK's?
JK's is fine, JK.
That's very distressing.
Good night.
Oh, don't make me feel like it's too late.
Don't be shy.
She'll take the feeling
That's what's so different about her.This is what made the difference in her troubles.
Let's move on to the announcement.
First, the washing material of your choice. Mr. Yasumoto.
Yes, sir.
Sauce for chilled Chinese noodles
As I said, I want to gather the team as a chilled Chinese noodles.
I have chosen the most decisive ingredient for the taste of chilled Chinese noodles, chilled Chinese noodles sauce.
First, washing desired ingredients Mr. Hoshina
Mr. Hoshina
I have chosen tomato.
The reason is that I think it is an excellent player that goes well with any sauce.
So I chose this one.
The first washing desired ingredient, Mr. Sakurai
Yes, sir.
I chose Chinese noodles.
It's good, isn't it? Up to here.
I'm making chilled Chinese noodles, so I can't start without them.
So I chose Chinese noodles.
First order of laundry ingredients: Mr. Hoshina.
Yes, sir.
Yes, Mr. Hoshina
Yes, Mr. Nakamura chose cucumber
Nakamura chose the cucumbers. From the first time I saw them, I knew they weren't from this planet, so I chose the cucumbers.
Success
Good, good
Why are you so nervous?
Please write down your second choice of laundry ingredients Please write down the second order of laundry materials you wish to use.
Second order of laundry materials Mr. Yasumoto
Mr. Yasumoto
Chinese noodles
I still want to make chilled chocolate
I want to make chilled chocolate
The second order of washing ingredients: Mr. Hoshinashi
Menz.
I want to make chilled choco.
I chose "Menz".
The second order of washing ingredients: Sakuraishi
Yes, I cooked an egg.
This is to recreate the chilled Chinese noodles at my house.
The second order of washing desired ingredients Mr. Nakamura
Yes, I chose the soy sauce die.
I got the paycheck, so I'd like to take the most as possible, but
But I thought I'd choose someone else.
Soy sauce die together.
No soy sauce die.
He said it was a cheap year.
What's a soy sauce die?
Yes, I have an opinion.
If you say something that's not in your vocabulary...
That means you don't care about this member.
No second order.
Add three packs.
Add four packs.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
You don't say.
of this script.
Isn't it good?
Yes. Maybe she can't read the writing on the whiteboard because of her eyesight.
Yes, but she can't see it, so I'll refer her here.
I see.
It's called "Omanure Soy Sauce Dimentu Curry.
Soy Sauce Dimentu Curry.
I see.
It's just a difference in perception. That's too bad.
Yes.
What'll you say next time, Mr. Isomoto?
No drunkenness
No Mr. Nakamura.
So I'll go in the third order.
I know it's a kouhei world.
Yes, sir.
Here are the Chinese noodles
Good.
They're gone
I want to take over Nakamura with this.
Yes, sir.
Three.
This hurts, Nakamura.
Now, the third ingredient of your choice, Mr. Yasumoto Now, the third order of choice, Mr. Yasumoto.
Red ginger
Adds color
It's coming.
You are a member of the royal road, aren't you?
Yes, sir.
Third ingredient of choice. Pears.
Lettuce.
Lettuce goes well with our members.
We're all on one team.
I chose lettuce here.
Third ingredient of choice, Mr. Sakurai
Mr. Sakurai
I chose sesame sauce.
There is only sesame sauce and curry left.
I thought it would be great if I didn't save the sesame sauce.
If I don't save the sesame sauce, it will be a big problem, so I chose the sesame sauce.
So I chose the sesame sauce.
Third choice of ingredients: Mr. Nakamura
Hmmm...
Oh, but then there's curry.
Oh, oh!
Goma (sesame)
Goma
I was going to choose sesame sauce.
But I thought, what if I'm covered with it here?
I gave up on her.
Well then, everyone, you've won the ingredients...
Isn't it amazing?Isn't that great?
I'll take it in fourth order.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
We will now move on. Fourth order of precedence, laundry desired material, Mr. Yasumoto.
Yes, sir. Green onions.
I knew you'd want it evenly distributed, well balanced, and with vegetables as well.
Both vegetables?
He wants to collect them.
Green and yellow, green and yellow curing.
Sharipan.
That's an artist.
Fourth order, laundry desired ingredients, no stars.
I think we've got a pretty good group of people.
Pam.
I thought it was time to eat meat, and I responded to your feelings there.
Fourth order, laundry desired ingredients, Gentleman Sakurai.
Yes, I'm exarelly good.
Um, grilled sauce.
Wait, wait for tempeh.
I know, right?
You want to eat yakitare, don't you?
I was thinking that this is quite irregular with the yakitare,
I was thinking, well, if I had grilled sauce, what kind of food would I like to eat?
The fourth order, washing desired ingredients, Nakamura Gentleman.
Yes, curry.
That's right.
Because I wanted to get the actual taste,
And there are some people who might be kind of disturbing me,
It was taken away.It was taken.
Yes, it is.
That's right.
They took the curry.
Yes, I did.
I tried to interfere.
Now, let's move on to the fifth order, which is the acquisition of everyone.
Let's move on to the fifth order of laundry materials, Mr. Yasumoto.
5th order of laundry materials: Mr. Hoshinashi
No, of course, Smubs.
We don't have a main paper yet.
I'm looking for that Shohei Otani.
5th in line, Mr. Yasumoto, laundry material.
No, of course, Smubs.
We don't have a main paper yet.
I'm looking for that Shohei Otani
Mr. Yasumoto, the 5th laundry material
No, of course, Mr. Smubs.
Mr. Sakurai.
5th, laundry material, Mr. Sakurai.
Yes, of course.
Keichi
IZAKENYAN
Keiichi is kind of amazing.
Everyone, since you were talking about "colorful, colorful, colorful"...
I thought I'd pay attention to color, too.
I chose red.
No problem, 5,000 yen!
The fifth order of laundry ingredients: Mr. Nakamura5th order of laundry desired ingredients Mr. Nakamura
Yes
Jangshu
I wanted to take the meat
Put on a shirt
I wanted to get some meat
But I wasn't a fan of fish sous-cherie
So we had to do chai shu
I had to play the chai chow.
I'm doing the watch, that's why I'm doing the chay shu.
Let's start with the pink box in the middle, Mr. Yasumoto and Mr. Hoshino.
We're going to win for sure!
Please take one piece of paper at a time.
I'll take the volume!
Winner!
We won the first game!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
Oh, I'm lost.
Please open the door then.
Please do.
Yes!
Come on!
All right! Good job!
Let's go for it!
Now, Mr. Yasumoto, who narrowly missed out... Now, Mr. Yasumoto, who was sorely missed, will
Please choose one more ingredient.
Is that okay?
Is it okay?
I would like to choose the Gyomic sausage.
I'll choose the Gyomic sausage.
Okay.
And finally, we'll move on to the sixth and final.
Oh, I see! I see what you mean.
The members are pretty bad!
I don't need that many men.
I don't need that many.
But I guess I'll take it...
And now, in the sixth order, Mr. Yasumoto, washerman's protective gear material.
Kanagawa
I still think this is the only one I have left.
I chose Kanagawa
n 6th round, choice of ingredient, no stars, I guess I'll have to make a salad, Parika
I chose "n", the 6th round choice of ingredient, Mr. Sakurai
I chose "book", my favorite of the remaining ingredients
n 6th round choice of ingredient Mr. Nakamura
Owner amaran
друз woman
I purchased it.
Now, Sakuraishi and Mr. Nakamura
In front of the pink box in the middle, please.
Yes, sir.
October Nakamura, please.
Please draw a rock-paper-scissors.
Whoever draws first, please make the first move. Make the one you pull first.
Yes, sir.
Okay, then, then.
We will sell some from Sakuraishi.
Yes, sir.
Then, please call us.
Oh, no! Oh no!
Games!
Cute!
Now, please return to your seats.
I was kind of expecting this result myself.
You can choose whichever you like, Yuta.
Oh, I'm fine either way.
Oh, do I have to put it in?
Oh, you can pretend that you didn't know about the rule I just mentioned.
You skipped the first or second one, didn't you? I made a mistake.
It was resurrected.
If you say so.
Is that okay?
You don't need it.
No, you can choose two.
Mr. Nakamura, these are the leftover ingredients.
You can choose between kiwi and pineapple.
Kiwi and pineapple, please.
Now that everyone has chosen their ingredients, let's move on to the actual eating phase.
Now, let us introduce each of the completed chilled chuka dishes.
This one is a little bit early and rustic as a result of aiming for the chilled chilled chuka,
But it is absolutely colorful and I think you can make a delicious chilled yashi-chuka.
This is not chilled chuka.
Soba style... soba... soba salad... soba? Soba style...soba...buckwheat salad...soba?
Soba...salad soba.
It's a chilled chilled chuka for healthy people.
Next, I made a hearty, kind of heavy chilled chilled chuka.
I thought I tried to make it colorful, but it turned out yellowish,
I thought I had thought about coloring it, but it turned out yellowish.
I don't know if there is an explanation for that.
Is there an explanation?
This one has curry stew, cucumber, chujuu, cucumber, and pineapple on top.
Yes.
What does it taste like? I can't imagine.
Let's eat it then.
Bon appétit.
Yes!
Well, it's the end of the lesson, after all. I'm hungry.
Hungry, hungry. That's a little scary.
Bon appétit.
It's like eating pork sirloin.
Really?
Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
How is it?
It's very good.
Hellaspuker?
Yes, Hellaspuker.
It's very good.
What about Emma?
I don't know, each one has its own character.
It's not bad. It's delicious, but a bit,
I guess I'm looking forward to it. I wonder if I'm looking forward to it.
My skin is showing.
Delicious.
It's delicious.
It's really sharp. I only had cucumber and chashu pork.
It's covered with curry.
Okay, I'll eat it.
How is it?
It tastes weird.
Yes, it does.
How about that fruit-scented udon?
Yup.
How about curry udon?
I'm sure the curry udon is delicious.
Curry udon?
Not enough curry?
No curry.
Oh!
Interesting.
There's no curry over there.
I put curry on everything.
I think the most important thing to leave out was the chashu pork.
On the contrary.
But if it's curry and udon with chashu, it's a lie.
What?
I liked the chashu so much. The cucumber goes well with the curry.
Delicious? It goes with curry! Delicious? It goes well with curry!
I serve it all to two people and eat it for dessert.
It's not so much the aftertaste as it is the cucumber that gets stuck on it once it's done.
Wow!
The fruit in the bento is much different.
It's like it's stained a little bit.
I can't find the pineapple!
It's not there too much!
See you in the next video!
Besides the memories, everyone is hungry and wants more.
Because we're running out of kiwi.
If you leave them out, they'll melt into the kiwi curry.
The kiwi will soak up more and more of the flavor.
It's not going to taste good anymore.
Is that chilled Chinese noodles good?
It's delicious.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
What do you think? Now...
It's not really yakitori.
I thought I'd eat it alone.
But we're really hungry.
I think we'll eat it.
So...
Chilled Chinese Draft
I think this one is probably the most comprehensive
I think it was Yasumoto-san's that put it all together the best.
thank you so much!
I wish we could have had it during the day
We're so different, we're so differentBecause we're different things. We are.
Yes, we are.
Rie's looks delicious.
Yes, it does.
The baseball team's team teacher called them "Buckeyes.
That's true.
I have a lot of cravings right now.
I have a massive desire to eat right now.
I think I just need to think a little bit more.
Yuna worked the hardest.
I tried my best
Please eat curry udon with leftover curry
Yes, sir.
I can't make good curry udon.
Delicious!
So, that's all.
That's all for now.
Bye bye!
BGM